Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Collection Additions, II.
  - Westmoreland County - County Payroll, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Westmoreland County - Paul Garver Grievance, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Westmoreland County - Rinier Discharge, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Westmoreland County - McKluren Discharge, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Westmoreland County - Wage Equity Committee - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Westmoreland County - Westmoreland Manor - Pay Hike News Clippings, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Westmoreland County - Paul Garver Grievance, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Westmoreland County - Sirkoch Discharge, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Westmoreland County - Howell Grievance, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Westmoreland County - Grievances, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Westmoreland County - Juvenile Detention Center - Agreement, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Westmoreland County - Education Committee - Reimbursement, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Westmoreland County - Tax Mapping Research, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - PT Schedules (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Beaver County - Settlement with SEIU, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Beaver County - Health Care Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Beaver County - Jail - Pay Scale/Agreements, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Beaver County - Court - Pay Scale/Dues, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Beaver County - Agreements/Correspondence, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Beaver County - Clerical-Technical Unit - Officer's Elections, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Beaver County - Grievances, 1985-1986 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Beaver County - Correspondence/Notes, 1981-1987 (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Beaver County - Ardisky Grievance, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 36)
  - Beaver County - Airport - Agreements with SEIU, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 37)
  - Beaver County - Grievances, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 38)
  - Beaver County - New Employee Reports, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 39)
  - CCAC - Internal Organization - List of Employees, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - CCAC - Bargaining Issues, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - CCAC - Negotiation Notes, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - CCAC - Trustees' Meetings - Minutes and Agenda, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - CCAC - Negotiation with SEIU, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - CCAC - Benefit Grievances, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - CCAC - Staffing Reports, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - CCAC - Contract - Final Draft, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - CCAC - Dues, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - CCAC - Steward Meeting - Notes, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - CCAC - Healthcare Meetings, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - CCAC - Correspondence - Memos, Grievances, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - CCAC - Correspondence - Memos, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - SEIU - AFT - Computing Suite - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - CCAC - Grievances, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - CCAC - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - CCAC - Hardwick Grievance, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - CCAC - Eagle Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - CCAC - Custodial-Maintenance - Allegations, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - CCAC - Custodial-Maintenance - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - CCAC - Custodial-Maintenance - Grievances, 1987-1988 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - CCAC - Custodial-Maintenance - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - CCAC - Custodial-Maintenance - Shift Changes, 1986-1987 (Box 118, Folder 23-24)
  - CCAC - Parrott Grievance, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - CCAC - Smelutz Grievance, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - CCAC - McLaughlin Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - CCAC - Eagle Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - CCAC - Smith Grievance, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 29)
  - CCAC - Chalmers Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - CCAC - Alexander Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - CCAC - Roberts Grievance, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - CCAC - Sullivan Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - CCAC - Williams Grievance, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - CCAC - Johnson Seniority Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - CCAC - Greene Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 36)
  - CCAC - Lawler Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 37)
  - CCAC - Keith Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 38)
  - CCAC - Wade Grievance, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 39)
  - CCAC - Fred Williams Grievance, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 40)
  - SEIU - Fair Share Tax Plan - Information, Memos, Notices, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dues Increase/Financial Research, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - McKeesport Hospital - Annual Report and Healthcare Research, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Dues Increase Correspondence, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO - AFL-CIO News - 1 Issue, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - IBM - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - McKeesport Hospital - RN's Negotiations, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - McKeesport Hospital - Final Cost Reports, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Washington School District - Negotiations, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Trinity Area School District - Leahy Grievance, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Apollo-Ridge School District - Custodial-Maintenance - Contract Agreements, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Sick Leave Correspondence, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Scott Grievance, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Burton Grievance, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Anthony Grievance, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - V. Polojac Grievance, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Southmoreland School District - Meetings/Negotiations, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Trinity Area School District - Smith-Mazza Suspension Grievance, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital - Grievances, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Arbitrations, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Apollo-Ridge School District - Contract Agreements, 1982-1983 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Murray Manor - Correspondence (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Murray Manor - Grievances, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Servicemaster, Inc. - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Trinity Middle School - Officer's/Steward's Elections, 1985 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Contract Agreements, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Board Elections, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Negotiations and Agreements, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Terminations/Warnings/Hirings, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Grievance Forms, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Trinity Area School District - Election Ballots (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Negotiations and Agreements, 1987-1990 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Southeastern Greene School District - Agreement/Seniority List, 1981 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Apollo-Ridge School District - Custodial Contract, 1982 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital - Grievances, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital - Contract, 1984-1986 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital - Discipline, 1980, 1985 (Box 121, Folder 6-7)
  - Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital - Arbitrations, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Allegheny County - Arbitrations, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Grievances, 1979 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Sunnyview Home - Contract Agreement, 1983-1984 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Greene County Memorial Hospital - Contract Agreement, 1981-1983 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - SEIU - Contract Proposals, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Arbitrations, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Beaver Valley Geriatrics Center - Hirings/Pay Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Convention - Agenda and Convention Materials, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - SEIU - Political Candidate Research, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - SEIU - Labor News Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence - Election News, Notices, Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Election - Candidate Pamphlets, 1986-1988 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - SEIU - Nursing Home Reform, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Collective Bargaining Testimonies, 1986-1987 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - SEIU - Medicare Testimonies, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Medicare Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Medicare Research, 1982-1985 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - SEIU - Healthcare Advisory Committee - Notices, Memos, Research, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Beverly Enterprises - Beverly Campaign Guidelines, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Beverly Enterprises - Agreements and Settlements with SEIU, 1985-1987 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - SEIU 1199/668 - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Murray Manor - Employee Attitude Surveys, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Beverly News Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - SEIU - Beverly Campaign Flyers, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Beverly Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 7-8)
  - NLRB - Beverly Hearings, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 9-11)
  - SEIU - Union of the Eighties - Campaign Materials (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - US Senate - Bill No. 293 Report (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Contract Summaries, 1985-1986 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - NY Public Employee Federation - Newsletter and Notices, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - SEIU - New Steward's Kit, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Citizens for Tax Justice - Tax Reports, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - SEIU - 8th Annual Western Women's Conference - Conference Materials, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Local Financial State, Grievances, Election Results, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - SEIU - Eastern Conference Convention - Reports, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Medicare - Reports, Correspondence, Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - American Assembly - 73rd Constitution Assembly - Reports, Summary, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - SEIU - Politics Is Union Business - Campaign Materials, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - SEIU - Labor Research, Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - SEIU - News Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - AFL-CIO - News Conference, Legislative News, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Pamphlets and Flyers (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Correspondence - Notices, Memos, Inquiries, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - SEIU - Labor News - Local 585 News, The Federationist, Local 509 News, 1986-1987 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Michael Dukakis - Campaign Posters, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Monsour Medical Center - Revised Pay Scale, 1975 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Democratic National Convention - Reports, Candidate Information, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - SEIU - Correspondence - Notices, Reports, Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - SEIU - Rossi - Expense Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 126, Folder 5-7)
  - SEIU - Rubin - Expense Reports, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - SEIU Local 585 - PA Human Resource Coalition Trial, 1984-1985 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - SEIU - Correspondence - News, Reports, Memos, Notices, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - PA Employment Security Association - Financial Statements, 1986 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - SEIU - Dukakis Campaign Information, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Membership Cards (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Toner Institute - Correspondence - Letters, Memos, Notices, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Toner Institute - Contract - Signed, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Toner Institute - Contract - Old, 1972 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Toner Institute - Contract - Working Copy, 1976-1977 (Box 127, Folder 5-6)
  - Toner Institute - Legal Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Toner Institute - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Penn State University - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Certificate of Representatives, 1970-1972 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Local 29 - Contracts, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - SEIU Local 585 - Certificate of Representatives, 1985-1998 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Local 585 - List of Members, 1999 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Toner Institute - Contract Agreement, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - SEUI and 1199 Healthcare Workers Affiliation, 1985-1988 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 128)
  - Cope Dinner and Staff Negotiations, 1980s, 1994 (Box 129)
  - Regional Labor Councils (Box 130)
  - Elections and Staff Assignments (Box 131)
  - Beverly Lawsuit, 1990s-2000 (Box 132)
  - Fair Share Fee Law Case, 1993 (Box 133)
  - Fair Share Fee Law Challenge, 1993-1994 (Box 134)
  - Contracts, Working Copies, A-C, 1980s (Box 135)
  - Contracts, Working Copies, D-W, 1980s (Box 136)
  - Signed Contracts, A-B, 1980s (Box 137)
  - Signed Contracts, B-G, 1980s (Box 138)
  - Signed Contracts, N-W, 1980s (Box 139)
  - Contracts, A-C, 1990s (Box 140)
  - Contracts, C-P, 1990s (Box 141)
  - Contracts, R-Z, 1990s (Box 142)
  - Shop Files, W, 1990s (Box 143)
  - Legal, McKeesport Hospital and Washington County, 1980s-1990s (Box 144)
  - Healthcare Initiative and Beverly Lawsuit, 1990s (Box 145)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1990s-2002 (Box 146-147)
  - Allegheny County, 1998-2000 (Box 148)
  - Office Files, 1970s-1990s (Box 149)
  - Organization, Legal, and Negotiations, 1980s-1990s (Box 150)
  - Office Files, 1980s-1990s (Box 151)
  - Beverly Lawsuit, 1990s (Box 152)
  - Political Action and Research, 1980s (Box 153)
  - Allegheny County, Negotiations, 1988 (Box 154)
  - Publications, 1980s-2003 (Box 155)
  - Manuals and Handbooks, 1980s-2000 (Box 156)
  - Reports and Papers, 1980s-2000 (Box 157)
  - Convention and Conference Materials (Box 158)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, Contract Agreements, and Legislative Directories (Box 159)
  - Video and Audio Tapes (Box 160)
  - Pins and Buttons (Box 161)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 162)
  - Photographs (Box 163-164)
  - Political Action and Newsletters (Agency Shop), 1981-1982 (Box 165)
  - Political Action and Research, Election Material and Privatization, 1995-1997 (Box 166)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1980s-1990s (Box 167)
  - Speeches and Labor Studies (Box 168)
  - Publications (Box 169)
  - Research (Box 170)
  - T-Shirts (Box 171)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1990s (Box 172)
  - SEIU 585 News Photographs, 1973-1974 (Box 173-174)